[

](https://succulentalley.com/)

Search

[

](https://succulentalley.com/)

Search

Toggle Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

At Succulent Alley, accessible from http://succulentalley.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Succulent Alley and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Succulent Alley. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. Our Privacy Policy was created with the help of the [Privacy Policy Generator](https://www.privacypolicygenerator.info/) and the [Free Privacy Policy Generator](https://www.generateprivacypolicy.com/#wizard).

Consent
-------

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

Information we collect
----------------------

The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.

When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number.

How we use your information
---------------------------

We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

* Provide, operate, and maintain our webste
* Improve, personalize, and expand our webste
* Understand and analyze how you use our webste
* Develop new products, services, features, and functionality
* Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the webste, and for marketing and promotional purposes
* Send you emails
* Find and prevent fraud

Log Files
---------

Succulent Alley follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

Cookies and Web Beacons
-----------------------

Like any other website, Succulent Alley uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.

For more general information on cookies, please read [“What Are Cookies” from Cookie Consent](https://www.cookieconsent.com/what-are-cookies/).

Our Advertising Partners
------------------------

Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.

* Google [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)

Advertising Partners Privacy Policies
-------------------------------------

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Succulent Alley.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Succulent Alley, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Succulent Alley has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Third Party Privacy Policies
----------------------------

Succulent Alley’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)
---------------------------------------------------------

Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:

Request that a business that collects a consumer’s personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.

Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.

Request that a business that sells a consumer’s personal data, not sell the consumer’s personal data.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

GDPR Data Protection Rights
---------------------------

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.

The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.

The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

Children’s Information
----------------------

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Succulent Alley does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Mediavine Programmatic Advertising (Ver 1.1)

The Website works with Mediavine to manage third-party interest-based advertising appearing on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use first and third-party cookies. A cookie is a small text file which is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so that a website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website.

First party cookies are created by the website that you are visiting. A third-party cookie is frequently used in behavioral advertising and analytics and is created by a domain other than the website you are visiting. Third-party cookies, tags, pixels, beacons and other similar technologies (collectively, “Tags”) may be placed on the Website to monitor interaction with advertising content and to target and optimize advertising. Each internet browser has functionality so that you can block both first and third-party cookies and clear your browser’s cache. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, how to disable existing cookies and how to clear your browser’s cache. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [All About Cookies](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

Without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of the Website content and features. Please note that rejecting cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site. In the event you opt-out, you will still see non-personalized advertisements on the Website.

The Website collects the following data using a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP Address
* Operating System type
* Operating System version
* Device Type
* Language of the website
* Web browser type
* Email (in hashed form)

Mediavine Partners (companies listed below with whom Mediavine shares data) may also use this data to link to other end user information the partner has independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements. Mediavine Partners may also separately collect data about end users from other sources, such as advertising IDs or pixels, and link that data to data collected from Mediavine publishers in order to provide interest-based advertising across your online experience, including devices, browsers and apps. This data includes usage data, cookie information, device information, information about interactions between users and advertisements and websites, geolocation data, traffic data, and information about a visitor’s referral source to a particular website. Mediavine Partners may also create unique IDs to create audience segments, which are used to provide targeted advertising.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [National Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://thenai.org/opt-out/). You may also visit [Digital Advertising Alliance website](https://optout.aboutads.info/#/) and [Network Advertising Initiative website](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/#) to learn more information about interest-based advertising. You may download the AppChoices app at [Digital Advertising Alliance’s AppChoices app](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out in connection with mobile apps, or use the platform controls on your mobile device to opt out.

For specific information about Mediavine Partners, the data each collects and their data collection and privacy policies, please visit [Mediavine Partners](https://www.mediavine.com/ad-partners/).

© 2024 Succulent Alley

[

](https://www.dmca.com/Protection/Status.aspx?ID=4b05f295-c2a9-4ca2-9841-8bb1e12c3049 "DMCA.com Protection Status")

[

](https://www.facebook.com/sharer/sharer.php?u=https%3A%2F%2Fsucculentalley.com%2Fprivacy-policy)

[

](#)

  [Scroll to top](#wrapper) Scroll to top

Toggle Menu Close

Search for:  

Search
